Dragonheart: Vengeance is a fantasy, action,
adventure film directed by Ivan Silvestrini.
Lukas, a young farmer whose family is killed by savage raiders in the countryside, sets out on an epic quest for revenge,
forming an unlikely trio with a majestic dragon and a swashbuckling, sword-fighting mercenary, Darius.
Darius, played by Joseph Millson.
Lukas, played by Jack Kane.
King Razvan, played by Arturo Muselli.
Siveth (voice), played by Helena Bonham Carter.
The Snake, played by Carolina Carlsson.
The Scorpion, played by Tam Williams.
Dragonheart: Vengeance is a 2020 fantasy adventure
film directed by Ivan Silvestrini.
It is the third direct-to-video prequel of the 1996 film, Dragonheart.
The film begins before the events of Dragonheart: Battle
for the Heartfire, but ends after them.
It was released on Netflix, DVD, and Blu-ray on February 4, 2020.